[{"answer": "Well, both that what he said was actually inaccurate and also very dangerous.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "When you heard Todd Akin's comments, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, that is the key point.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "ORGAN: How would you have felt if you had been compelled to have that baby by the rapist who raped you?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "You know, modern America has said, according to the Supreme Court, that it is cruel and unusual punishment to give the death penalty for rapists.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Isn't that what a modern America should stand for?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "You know, I may not look the same as I did when I was 4 years old or 4 weeks old unborn in my mother's womb.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Why should that woman who feels that strongly the other way to you not have the same right that you did?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, let me just tell you, there -- you brought up people in a coma.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Well, what good is my right to anything as a woman if I don't have my right to life?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, what he said is despicable and outrageous, and it's good at least to see his own party trying to banish him from the race.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "And what does it mean for the presidential battle?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, what we've really argued in this book is we didn't get here by accident.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What is the core of the problem for America incorporated, when you look at it, do you think?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "You know, there's no question to me that we have to agree on one thing, that the only way to deal with the budget deficit that big is with both tax revenue and spending cuts.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "I mean, what -- when you look at the Ryan Budget Plan, Romney's amendment of that, you look at what President Obama is saying, what do you think is the most sensible way forward for America to finance all this?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I think they have an incredibly weak foreign policy biography between the two of them and a rather weak team, frankly.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Tom, when you hear Romney talking tough on Iran, and we've also got the Syria situation bubbling away as well, do you think that the Romney/Ryan ticket has enough foreign policy experience to know what to do about these two crises?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's a very legitimate question.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "And why shouldn't they assume it will be coming their way?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "The problem with Syria is that unlike other Arab awakening revolutions -- you know, Libya imploded.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Isn't it time that somebody did something?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Here's the thing, I'm a Christian, you're a Christian.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Yourself?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "We have a branding problem probably.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Do you feel that being Christian has become almost a bad word in a country that's still predominantly Christian?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Well, here's the -- I mean, I always avoided politics, especially as a comedian because you're alienating half the thing.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Has he lived up to the expectation, hopes that you had?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "He's a successful businessman.", "docId": "120821pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "For you, Romney is the more likely of the candidates?", "qSentId": 524}]